leechvideo.com 2010-02-17

# Privacy Policy - LeechVideo.com - Aggregate,Download and Convert hot videos of YouTube, MySpace Video,Google Video,etc.

## Effective Date: September 29, 2006

LeechVideo.com values your privacy. We recognize that you may be concerned about our collection, use, and disclosure of the personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that we collect when you use the Website and the services offered on the Website ("LeechVideo.com Services"). This Privacy Policy describes how we use and protect your personal information. By using the website you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [webmaster@LeechVideo.com](mailto:privacy@LeechVideo.com).

### General

Personal Information. We collect Personal Information that you provide to us, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, credit card number, and financial information.

Non-Personal Information. We also collect non-personal information from you, such as your browser type, the URL of the previous website you visited, your ISP, operating system, and your Internet protocol (IP) Address ("Non-Personal Information"). Non-Personal Information cannot be easily used to personally identify you.

### Use of information

When you register, we ask for your personal information and other information that we request during the registration process. If you communicate with us regarding the Website or the LeechVideo.com Services, we will collect any information that you provide to us in any such communication.

Like the operators of most websites, we may record Non-Personal Information such as Internet domain and host names, Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser software, operating system types, clickstream patterns, and the dates and times that the Website and the LeechVideo.com Services are accessed. For instance, we may use IP addresses we collected to help diagnose technical problems or prevent abuse of our systems or other site users. Your IP address may also be used to gather aggregate demographic data and target advertisements accordingly. 

A cookie is a small line of text that is stored with your web browser for record-keeping purposes and to help us provide better services to you. Your browser has options to accept, reject, or provide you with notice when a cookie is set. We use cookies to save your password on your machine so you don��t have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and track your downloads on our website. 

Personal Information. Once you give us your personal information, you consent to the transfer and storage of that information to our servers located in the United States. We use Personal Information primarily for our own internal purposes, such as providing, maintaining, evaluating, and improving the LeechVideo.com Services and the Website, fulfilling requests for information, producing and shipping the products that you order, and providing customer support. 

Non-Personal Information. We may disclose Non-Personal Information to improve the services we offer and facilitate our marketing efforts. In addition, we may combine multiple users�� Non-Personal Information to determine which areas of the Website are most popular, and how our services are used. In analyze the aggregate information, we can use it to improve the site and also see ways to improve our services.

### Disclosure of Your Information

Third Parties. We do not control the privacy policies of our advertisers or other third parties that have Web sites linked to the Site. If you click on an advertisement or link, the privacy policies of the Web site that you link to will govern the use of your information by that Web site's operator. We assume no responsibility or liability for the actions of such third parties with respect to their use of your information or otherwise. Accordingly, make sure you are aware of and comfortable with the privacy policies of any third-party Web sites you link to. In addition, you should be aware that certain third-party services or Web sites that you link to from our Web site each have their own information collection practices and privacy policies.

Disclosure Of Information In Public Areas. If you voluntarily disclose information in a public area of the Site, such as a message board, that information may be collected and used by a third party to send you unsolicited messages, advertisements or for other purposes. We do not control the actions of these third parties in public areas of the Site, so if you disclose information in a public area, you do so at your own risk.

No Absolute Safeguards. Although we will use reasonable efforts to safeguard the privacy of your information, transmissions on the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure. Accordingly, we assume no responsibility or liability for disclosure of any of your information due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third-party access or other causes beyond our reasonable control.

### Children Under 13

Our site is not directed to children under the age of 13. We assume products purchased through credit card means are purchased by adults. We respect the privacy of parents and children and are committed to complying with the Children Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). On those areas of the sites that ask for age, we do not collect personal information from individuals who identify themselves as under the age of 13 except in those limited circumstances where we believe that such collection is permitted under COPPA.

If a parent believes that his or her child has submitted personal information to us, he or she can contact us at [webmaster@LeechVideo.com](mailto:privacy@LeechVideo.com). We will promptly delete the information upon learning that it relates to a child under the age of 13. Please note that it is possible some of this information may remain archived in web logs and back-up archives after we delete the information from its active database. 

We believe that parents should supervise their children online activities and consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers that help provide a kid-friendly online environment. These tools can also prevent children from otherwise disclosing online their name, address and other personal information without parental permission.

### Opt-Out

We provide you the opportunity to opt-out of having your Personal Information used for certain purposes. For example, if you purchase a product/service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference on our order form.

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletters and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at [webmaster@LeechVideo.com](mailto:privacy@LeechVideo.com). We also offer you an opportunity to opt-out of certain communications through the account management screen. If you need assistance you may contact us at [webmaster@LeechVideo.com](mailto:privacy@LeechVideo.com); or via mail sent to 731 Market Street, Suite 600, San Francisco CA 94103.

If we disclose your Personal Information to a third party in a manner that is not set forth in this Privacy Policy you will be notified so that you can make an informed choice about sharing your Personal Information with that third party.

### General

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on this Website. All amended terms automatically take effect 30 days after they are initially posted on this Site.
